A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5 FA1403
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5
1956-2007
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council
JDR 3rd Fund
FA1403
208.06 Cubic Feet 540 containers
Arrangement
Records Group 5 Grants is arranged primarily alphabetically by subject in the following 21 series. Each series is then further arranged alphabetically by country of origin or record type.
Series 1: Grant Awards
Series 2: Grant Lists
Series 3: Archaeology
Series 4: Architecture
Series 5: Art Education
Series 6: Art History
Series 7: Arts Administration
Series 8: Cinematography-Photography
Series 9: Crafts
Series 10: Dance
Series 11: Design
Series 12: Exhibitons
Series 13: General Culture
Series 14: Literature
Series 15: Museology
Series 16: Music
Series 17: Painting and Sculpture
Series 18: Publications
Series 19: Theater
Series 20: Memorabilia
Series 21: Audio
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact a RAC archivist.
Scope and Contents
Record Group 5 is comprised of the grant administration files of the Asian Cultural Council, 1958-2007, including such files of the Asian Cultural Program of the JDR Fund which were inherited by the Council following the dissolution of the JDR Fund in 1979.
Grant‐making is the core of Asian Cultural Council operations. Through fiscal year 2008, the ACC has provided grant assistance to approximately 6,000 Asian and American artists, scholars and specialists in the arts, awarding approximately 100 grants per year.
Funding is provided in support of the following fields of study: Archaeology; Architecture; Art Education; Art History; Arts Administration; Cinematography; Crafts; Dance; Design; Exhibitions; General Culture; Literature; Museology; Music, Painting; Photography; Sculpture; and Theater.
- Grant Awards, 1975-1988; 1; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - US Information Agency (USIA), Budget Request FY 1986 (Box 414, Folder 1)
  - USIA, IA-22304-19-G, FY 1986 (Box 414, Folder 2)
  - USIA Funding, Letter of Credit, IA-22304-19-G, FY 1986 (Box 414, Folder 3)
  - USIA Grant, IA-22304-19-G, Narrative and Financial Final Reports, FY, 1986 (Box 414, Folder 4)
  - USIA Rupee Endowment Grant, DS-8609, IA-428-1182-G (Box 414, Folder 5)
  - USIA Funding Request, FY 1987, 1986 October 1-1987 September 30 (Box 414, Folder 6)
  - USIA Grant IA-PSMA-G7192785, FY 1987, 1986 October 1-1987 September 30 (Box 414, Folder 7)
  - USIA Grant IA-PSMA-G7192785, FY, Final Financial and Narrative Reports, 1987 (Box 414, Folder 8)
  - Smithsonian Institution No. 60835400, Final Narrative and Financial Reports, IAFP (Box 414, Folder 9)
  - ICA Grant IA-20111-19-G, 1982 January 1-September 30 (Box 414, Folder 10)
  - USIA IA-21628-19-G, FY 1985 (Box 414, Folder 11)
  - SC, American Secretariat, Ford Foundation Grant, 750-0510A (Box 414, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation Reports, 750-510A, Original-Final Narrative, FY 1988 (Box 414, Folder 13)
  - USIA Grant IA-PSMA-G7192785, Letter of Credit, FY 1987 (Box 414, Folder 14)
  - Coopers and Lybrand Audit, 1987 (Box 414, Folder 15)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, Planning, GP-21181-84 (Box 414, Folder 16)
  - Asian Cultural Council, Festival of India Grant (Box 415, Folder 1)
  - Funding, 1976 (Box 415, Folder 2)
  - CU Grant 1069-587195, Original Grant, 1975 May 21 (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - CU Grant 1069-587195, Third Amendment, 1976 September 30 (Box 415, Folder 4)
  - SFCP Grant 40619200, DS-8406, IAFP, 1984 June 1-1985 December 31 (Box 415, Folder 5)
  - Smithsonian, IAFP Request, 1984-1985 (Box 415, Folder 6)
  - USIA Audit, 1985 (Box 415, Folder 7)
  - Smithsonian Institution 41009400, Final Narrative and Financial Reports, 1985-1986 Joint Programs (Box 415, Folder 8)
  - Smithsonian Institution 60835400, IAFP, DS-8607, 1986 July 1-1987 December 31 (Box 415, Folder 9)
  - Smithsonian Institution Grant 20689300, IAFP, 1982-1983 (Box 415, Folder 10)
  - Smithsonian Institution 20494600, Joint Programs Grant, 1982-1983 (Box 415, Folder 11)
  - Proposal to Smithsonian, IAFP, 1981-1982 (Box 415, Folder 12)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Grant 41009400, Joint Programs, DS-8411 (Box 415, Folder 13)
  - Proposal to Smithsonian Institution, IAFP, 1985-1986 (Box 415, Folder 14)
  - Proposal to Smithsonian for Joint Programs, 1984 (Box 415, Folder 16)
  - SFCP Grant for Secretariat Support, 10524600, 1981-1982 (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Smithonisan Institution Grant 10567500 for IAFP, 1981-1982 (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - Smithsonian Institution Grant 20852400 for IAFP, 1982 September 8-1984 July 31 (Box 416, Folder 3)
  - Grant Request, Narrative and Budget, 1981 October 1-1982 September 30 (Box 416, Folder 4)
  - USIA Grant Agreement, FY 1983 (Box 416, Folder 5)
  - Price Waterhouse Audit, 1984-1986 (Box 416, Folder 6-7)
  - IAFP Funding, Smithsonian Grant, 90686100, 1979-1980 (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - ICA Grant, Secretariat Support, IA-19147-19G, FY 1979-1980 (Box 416, Folder 9)
  - IAFP Funding, NSF, Grant INT 79-00597, 1979-1980 (Box 416, Folder 10)
  - Secretariat Funding, Smithsonian Rs. Support for JM Meeting, 1978 March 2-3 (Box 416, Folder 11)
  - Smithsonian, SFCP, Request for Secretariat Programs, 90319500, 1978 October 5 (Box 416, Folder 12)
  - Fiscal Data, FY, 1977-1978 (Box 416, Folder 13)
  - Secretariat Funding, CU Grant 1069-7870, 2nd Amendment, 1978 March 28 (Box 417, Folder 1)
  - CU Grant 1069-787041, Original Grant, 1976 November 16 (Box 417, Folder 2)
  - CU Grant 1069-587195, First Amendment, 1976 March 25 (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - Request for Saivism Film, Smithsonian Institution FCP, 1979 (Box 417, Folder 4)
  - IAFP Funding, SI, FC 70669700, Award Letter, Amendment 1-4, 1977-1978 (Box 417, Folder 5)
  - ICA Grant 1069-787041, 3rd and 4th Amendment, 1978 June 20 (Box 417, Folder 6)
  - Second NSF, INT 7705038, Proposal, 1976-1979 (Box 417, Folder 7)
  - Second NSF Grant, INT 7705038, Award Letter, 1977-1979 (Box 417, Folder 8)
  - CU Grant 1069-587195, Final Report, 1976 June 14 (Box 417, Folder 9)
  - First NSF Grant, INT 7619024, Proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 417, Folder 10)
  - First NSF Grant, INT 7619024, Award Letter, 1976-1977 (Box 417, Folder 11)
  - NSF Grant 77-05038, Financial Reporting, 1977-1979 (Box 417, Folder 12)
  - CU Grant 1069-587195, Second Amendment, 1976 May 12 (Box 417, Folder 13)
  - Bangkok Meeting on Culture and the Arts, 1980 June 4 (Box 417, Folder 14)
- Grant Lists, 1958-1978; 2; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Reports Grants Listings, 1970-1973 (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - Reports Grants Listings, 1974-1978 (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Theatre Project (Box 418, Folder 3)
  - Non-Fund Projects, DHM, Archaeology, Burma-Pagan, 1958-1962 (Box 418, Folder 4)
  - Non-Fund Projects, Japan Expo, 1970 (Box 418, Folder 5)
  - Non-Fund Publications, Manuscript of Japanese Painting Today, Preface by Davis Kung, Statement by 50 Artists (Box 418, Folder 6)
  - Non-Fund Projects. Japanese House at the Museum of Modern Art, Survey by the American University (Box 419, Folder 1)
  - Grants Related to India, Corrections and Changes (Box 419, Folder 2)
  - Grants, Hong Kong, Copies (Box 419, Folder 3)
  - Grants: Thailand, Hong Kong, and Singapore, Changes and Corrections (Box 419, Folder 4)
  - Drafts, Thailand, Singapore, and Hong Kong (Box 419, Folder 5)
  - Grants: Thailand, Copies (Box 419, Folder 6)
  - Grants: Pakistan, Copies (Box 419, Folder 7)
  - Grants: India, Copies (Box 419, Folder 8)
  - Grants: Hong Kong, Summary, 1972 August 15 (Box 419, Folder 9)
  - Grants Lists: Corrections and Changes (Box 419, Folder 10)
  - Grants Lists: General (Box 419, Folder 11)
  - Corrections: Lists, 1973 January 26 (Box 419, Folder 12)
  - Grants: Pakistan, Drafts and Notes (Box 419, Folder 13)
  - Grants: Korea, Drafts and Notes (Box 419, Folder 14)
  - Various Grant Lists by Country, Prepared by JDR 3rd Fund, 1972 (Box 419, Folder 15)
  - Contemporary Indian Painting, Various Artists (Box 419, Folder 16)
  - Grant Lists for Cambodia, China, Philippines and Taiwan (Box 633, Folder 5)
- Archaeology, 1964-1997; 3; 7.22 Cubic Feet 19 letter document boxes
  - Afghanistan, 3.1
    Afghanistan
    - Rose, Roger G.,DF-6545, 1965 (Box 419, Folder 17)
  - Asia, 3.2
    Asia
    - Francis, Peter, Jr., DF-9297, 1992 (Box 419, Folder 18)
    - Indo-Pacific Prehistory Association, 702-00-98012-203.2 (Box 420, Folder 1)
  - Bangladesh, 3.3
    Bangladesh
    - Qadir, Abdul, University of Amsterdam, DF-7288, B-72106, B-7405, B-7306, DF-7411 (Box 420, Folder 2)
  - Cambodia, 3.4
    Cambodia
    - East-West Center, 702-00-96057-203.000-1 (Box 420, Folder 3)
    - East-West Center, Tea Van, 702-00-97064-203.000-1 (Box 420, Folder 4)
    - Bong, Sovath, 702-00-71079-203.1, 100-00-2206-203.3 (Box 420, Folder 5)
  - China, 3.5
    China
    - Dupree, Louis, EC-7867, 1978 (Box 420, Folder 6)
    - Adams, William, B-88114(56)R, 1988 (Box 420, Folder 7)
    - Murowchick, Robert, EC-8890(56)R, 1988 (Box 420, Folder 8)
    - China Institute in America, DF-9103, 1991 (Box 421, Folder 1)
    - Pigott, Vincent, EC-8676(56)R, 1986 (Box 421, Folder 2)
    - Solhelm, Wilhelm G. DF-9202, 1992 (Box 421, Folder 3)
    - Leng, Jian, B-8512, DF-8613, R-8240(71) (Box 421, Folder 4)
    - Wang, Wenjin, B-9033(26), B-9129(26) (Box 421, Folder 5)
    - White, Joyce, EC-8677(56)R, 1986 (Box 421, Folder 6)
    - Kamberi, Dolkun, 706-00-97074-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 421, Folder 7)
    - Yang, Hong, 702-00-97009-203.000-2, 1997 (Box 421, Folder 8)
    - Zhang, Zhong-pei, 100-00-96021-203.000-3, 483-00-95045-203.000-1 (Box 422, Folder 1)
    - An, Jiayao, 100-00-21011-203.3 (Box 422, Folder 2)
    - An, Jiayao, 100-00-98035-203.3 (Box 422, Folder 3)
    - An, Jiayao, B-8831, 1988 (Box 422, Folder 4)
    - Peng, Shifan, 702-00-97008-203.000-2, 1997 (Box 422, Folder 5)
    - An, Jiayao, 702-00-24055-203.1 (Box 422, Folder 6)
    - Zhang, Yinglan, 702-00-24057-203.1 (Box 422, Folder 7)
  - Hong Kong, 3.6
    Hong Kong
    - Chau, Hing-Wah, B-9257(383), B-9258 (HK), 1992 (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - India, 3.7
    India
    - Rajan, K. V. Soundara (Mr.), DF-71105, 1971 (Box 423, Folder 2)
    - Asthana, Shashi Prabha, DF-7682, 1976 (Box 423, Folder 3)
    - Chakrabarti, Dilip Kumar, DF-7682, 1976 (Box 423, Folder 4)
    - Nienu, Vikuosa, B-7135, B-7614, B-7714, B7811, B-7851, R-8021, File I (Box 424, Folder 1)
    - Nienu, Vikuosa, EC-8047-MCR (File II), 1980 (Box 423, Folder 5)
    - Urban Dwelling Environments, Ahmedabad, India, Nimish Patel (Box 424, Folder 2)
    - Vijayanagra Archaeology Project, B-8569, 1985 (Box 424, Folder 3)
    - Bhan, Kuldeep, B-9233, 1992 (Box 424, Folder 4)
    - Balasubramanya, B-9254(26), 1992 (Box 425, Folder 1)
    - Medhi, Dilip K., B-8933, 1989 (Box 425, Folder 2)
    - Rosen, Elizabeth S., B-7355, 1973 (Box 937, Folder 5)
  - Indonesia, 3.8
    Indonesia
    - Seoul National University, Archaeology-Indonesia, B-7445, 1974 (Box 425, Folder 3)
    - Asian Institution Purchases, Asian Specialists and Institutions, General Culture-Asia, B-7445, 1974 (Box 425, Folder 4)
    - University Museum (PA.) and Archaeological, Institute of Indonesia, Archaeology-Indonesia, B-7367, 1973 (Box 425, Folder 5-6)
    - New York University, Borobudur, EC-6860 (Box 426, Folder 2)
    - Borobudur, Reconstruction-Fund Raising Correspondence (Box 426, Folder 3)
    - Borobudur, Reconstruction-Fund Raising Correspondence, EC-6860 (Box 426, Folder 4)
    - Jajasan Purbakala and S. Suleiman (Mrs.), B-6833, DF-7082, DF-7294 (Box 426, Folder 2)
    - Soediman (Mr.), B-7035 (Box 426, Folder 3)
    - Soejono, R. P., VIII CIASE (Inernational Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences), Japan, September 1968, DF-68104 (Box 426, Folder 4)
    - Soekmono, R. (Mr.), 28th International Congress of Orientalists, Canberra, Australia, DF-7072, DF-7179, 1971 January (Box 426, Folder 5)
    - Sutayasa, I. Made (Mr.), ANZAAS Congress, Perth Australia, DF-73103, 1973 August (Box 426, Folder 6)
    - University Museum and National Archaeological, Institute of Indonesia, Training, Bennet Bronson, Lembaga Purbakala dan Penunggalan Nasional, B-7544, B-7367-MCR, B-7544 (Box 426, Folder 7)
    - Borobudur, Archaeology-Indonesia, Reports, EC-6860, 1968 (Box 426, Folder 1)
    - Borobadur, EC-6860, 1968 (Box 427, Folder 1)
    - Indonesia Archaeology Project, Ford Foundation, R-8332(29), 1983 (Box 427, Folder 8)
    - Indonesia Archaeology Project, Ford Foundation, R-8135 (9), Donation D-8109, 1981 (Box 428, Folder 1)
    - Ford Foundation, John Miksic Travel Grant, R-8246(23), 1982 (Box 428, Folder 2)
    - Miksic, J., DD-8564(49)R, 1985 (Box 428, Folder 3)
    - Solhim, Wilhelm G., B-9055(56), 1990 (Box 428, Folder 4)
    - Jajasan Purbakala, DF-7082, B6833, 1968; 1970 (Box 937, Folder 6)
    - University Museum, University of Pennsylvania and Archaeological Institute of Indonesia, B-7367, 1973 (Box 938, Folder 1)
  - Japan, 3.9
    Japan
    - Brill, Robert H., DF-90111, 1990 (Box 428, Folder 5)
    - Namba, Junko, 702-00-23051-203.1 (Box 429, Folder 1)
  - Korea, 3.10
    Korea
    - Choi, Mong-Lyong (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - Choi, Mong-Lyong, B-7919, B-8014, B-8041 (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Pai, Hyung Il, B-8215, 1982 (Box 429, Folder 4)
    - Choi, Mong-Lyong, B-8115, 1981 (Box 429, Folder 5)
    - Bae, Kidong, B-8840, 1988 (Box 430, Folder 1)
    - Kim, Won-Yong, University of London, B-6888, 1968 (Box 430, Folder 2)
    - Sohn, Pow-key, DF-6802, 1968 (Box 430, Folder 3)
    - Seoul National University (Kim, Won-Yong), B-7455, DF-7552, 1974-1975 (Box 938, Folder 2)
  - Malaysia, 3.11
    Malaysia
    - O'Connor, Stanley J., B-6618, 1966 (Box 430, Folder 4)
    - Buyong, Kamarul, DF-9220, DF-9201, EC-9110(26), B-9134(26), B-8949(26), B-8856(26)R (Box 431, Folder 4)
  - Nepal, 3.12
    Nepal
    - Howland, Richard, B-7049, 1970 (Box 430, Folder 5)
    - Protective Inventory of Kathmandu Valley, B-7175-MCR, 1971 (Box 430, Folder 6)
    - Protective Inventory of Kathmandu Valley, B-7175-MCR (Box 945, Folder 3)
    - Thapa, Ramesh, (IIE), EC-6855, Book Request see Folder 2, Department of Archaeology (Box 430, Folder 7)
    - Sekler, Eduard F., Harvard University, Durbar Square Preservation, EC-7486, DF-7952 (Box 430, Folder 8)
    - Department of Archaeology Book Request, Book 2, EC-6855, B70103 (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - Archaeology, Nepal, Protective Inventory of Kathmadu Valley, Prusch C., B-7175-MCR, 1971 (Box 431, Folder 2)
    - Khanal, Mohan Prasad, B-8523(26)R, 1985 (Box 431, Folder 3)
  - Pakistan, 3.13
    Pakistan
    - Mughal, M. Qafique, EC-7017, DF-7758, B-6776, DF-6910 (Box 431, Folder 5)
    - Hassan, Iqbal, University of Pennsylvania, B-7138, B-7219, B7322, B-7426, B-7527, DF-7656, DF-73105 (Box 431, Folder 6)
    - University Museum, University of Pennsylvania, Dales, George F., B-6418, DF-7282, EC-7871, 1964-1978 (Box 938, Folder 3)
  - Philippines, 3.14
    Philippines
    - Dalupan, Maria, EC-88103(26)R, 1988 (Box 431, Folder 7)
  - Thailand, 3.15
    Thailand
    - Silpakorn University, Faculty of Archaeology Library, B-7258 AIP, 1972 (Box 432, Folder 1)
    - Charoenwongsa, Pisit, B-7626, 1976 (Box 432, Folder 2)
    - Fine Arts Department (Box 432, Folder 3)
    - Pookajorn, Surin, DF-8137, 1981 (Box 432, Folder 4)
    - Charoenwongsa, B-7626, DF-7680, B-7732, 1976-1977 (Box 938, Folder 4)
    - Fine Arts Department of Thailand, EC-7873, 1978 (Box 939, Folder 1)
    - University Museum, University of Pennsylvania, B-6961, 1969 (Box 939, Folder 2)
  - Vietnam, 3.16
    Vietnam
    - Khoach, Nguyen Ba, EC-7760, B-7834, B-8103, B-8121 (Box 432, Folder 5)
    - Khoach, NguyenBa, R-8314(7), B-8518 (Box 432, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Science Congress Project, R-8231(7), 1982 (Box 433, Folder 1)
    - Indo-Pacific Prehistory Association, B-9371(560, EC-9007(26), DF-8471 (Box 433, Folder 2)
    - Indo-Pacific Prehistory Association, 706-00-22092-203.1 (Box 433, Folder 3)
    - International Center for East Asian Archaeology and Cultural History (Box 433, Folder 4)
- Architecture, 1964-1999; 4; 8.73 Cubic Feet 23 letter document boxes
  - Afghanistan, 4.1
    - Samizay, Mohanned Rafi, Architecure-Afghanistan (Box 433, Folder 5)
    - Samizay, Mohammad Rafi, B-74048, B-7334, DF-47112 (Box 434, Folder 1)
    - Kabul University, DF-7183, 1971 (Box 434, Folder 2)
  - Asia, 4.2
    - International Congress on Religion, Architecture and the Visual Arts, Other Than Correspondence, DF-6786, 1967 (Box 434, Folder 3)
    - International Congress on Religion, Architecture and the Visual Arts, DF-6786, 1967 (Box 434, Folder 4)
    - National Architectural Accrediting Board, James A. Foley, DF-7487, 1974 (Box 434, Folder 5)
    - Harvard, University, Urban Design Program, 5 students- Ho, Chi-wing, Iwasaki, Shunsuke, Namioko, Sakura, Oommen, George, Pang, Wing Ning, DF-77077, 1969-1970 (Box 434, Folder 6)
    - Pelzer, Dorothy (Box 434, Folder 7)
    - Architectural League of New York, 706-00-97084-203.1 (Box 434, Folder 8)
    - Pelzer, Dorothy Project, File IV, B-8048 MCR, 1980 (Box 434, Folder 9)
    - Smithsonian Institution, Pelzer Project, EC-8705, EC-9306 (Box 435, Folder 1-2)
    - Belluardo, James, 706-00-95062-203.000-1 (Box 435, Folder 3)
    - Chapman, William, 706-22-21093-203.1 (Box 435, Folder 4)
    - Pelzer, Dorothy, B-6823, B-7152, EC-7930, 1968-1979 (Box 939, Folder 3)
    - Pelzer, Dorothy, B-6823, B-7152, EC-7930, B-8048 MCR, 1968-1980 (Box 939, Folder 4)
    - Pelzer, Dorothy, B-8048 MCR, 1980 (Box 940, Folder 1)
  - Bangladesh, 4.3
    - Abedin, Saiful, University of California-Berkeley, B-7305, 1973 (Box 435, Folder 5)
    - Ahmad, Ajmal H., B-7603, 1976 (Box 435, Folder 6)
  - Cambodia, 4.4
    - (Khmer), Som, Salism B-7407, 1974 (Box 435, Folder 7)
    - Columbia University, DF-8545, 1985 (Box 435, Folder 8)
    - Chapman, William, 479-00-95115-203.000-1 (Box 435, Folder 9)
    - World Monuments Fund, Lek Sareth, 702-00-96011-203.00-2 (Box 436, Folder 1)
  - China, 4.5
    - Pan, Sze-Chiu, B-681 (Box 436, Folder 2)
    - Ai, Fu Brice, B-7604, 1976 (Box 436, Folder 3)
    - Mi, Davis I-Cheng, B-7607, 1976 (Box 436, Folder 4)
    - Hsu, Chu-Tzu, B-7605, 1976 (Box 436, Folder 5)
    - Chau, Kenneth T. H., B-7706, 1977 (Box 436, Folder 6)
    - King, O. P. (Jin Oubu), DF-8306, 1983 (Box 436, Folder 7)
    - Wu, Huanjia, B-8572, 1985 (Box 436, Folder 8)
    - Fowler, John, DF-8822, 1988 (Box 436, Folder 9)
    - Fu, Xinian, B-8745(26)R, 1987 (Box 436, Folder 10)
    - Hack, Gary, B-8511, 1985 (Box 437, Folder 1)
    - Herdeg, Klaus, DF-8132 B-9264(56), 1981 (Box 437, Folder 2-3)
    - Chen, Arthur Hui-Min, 706-00-96063-203.000-1 (Box 437, Folder 4)
    - Wang, Shaosen, 505-00-96106-203.000-4 (Box 437, Folder 5)
    - Zhuang, Weimin, 464-00-94093-203.000-4 (Box 437, Folder 6)
    - Abramson, Daniel, 494-00-96117-203.1 (Box 437, Folder 7)
    - An, Qingdong, 566-00-99029-203.4, 566-00-98127-203.4, 571-00-98125-203.4 (Box 437, Folder 8)
    - Huang, Yiru, 507-00-97092-203.000-1 (Box 438, Folder 1)
    - Hu, Rongrui, 654-00-22139-203.4 (Box 438, Folder 2)
    - Lai, Delin, 702-00-95011-203.000-1 (Box 438, Folder 3)
    - Shan, Jun, 650-00-22049-203.4, 630-00-21087-203.1 (Box 439, Folder 1)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 702-00-22150-203.1, 100-00-22152-203.3 (Box 439, Folder 2)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 706-00-211011-203.1 (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 706-00-20092-203.1 (Box 439, Folder 4)
    - Wang, Yi, 100-00-21016-203.2, 609-00-20139-203.4 (Box 439, Folder 5)
    - Zhou, Cunya, 566-00-99030-203.4, 571-00-98126-203.4, 566-00-98128-203.4 (Box 440, Folder 1)
    - Caputo, Steven, 706-00-25009-203.2 (Box 440, Folder 2)
    - Liang, Wei, 688-00-23118-203.4 (Box 440, Folder 3)
    - Williams, John, 706-00-23066-203.1 (Box 440, Folder 4)
    - Wu, Tinghai, 736-00-24132-203.4 (Box 440, Folder 5)
    - Liu, Dimon, DF-7846, 1978 (Box 940, Folder 2)
  - Hong Kong, 4.6
    - Pang, Wing Ning, Harvard University, EC-7114, 1971 (Box 440, Folder 6)
    - Architecture-China, Wong, Joseph On-Woo, B-7610, 1976 (Box 440, Folder 7)
    - Ip, Kwok-Bun, B-8622, 1986 (Box 440, Folder 8)
    - Chu, Nelson, DD-90113(318), 1990 (Box 440, Folder 9)
    - Chan Corrin Chui Yi, B-8975(59), 1989 (Box 441, Folder 1)
    - Change, Gary Chee Keung, 522-00-97024-203.4 (Box 441, Folder 2)
    - Chan, Lai Kiu, 464-00-94013-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 441, Folder 3)
    - Lau, Patrick Sau Shing, DD-9228(388), 1992 (Box 441, Folder 4)
    - Liu, William, DD-93102(404), 1993 (Box 441, Folder 5)
    - Ng, Vincent Wing Shun, 484-00-95103-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 441, Folder 6)
    - Pong, Anthony Yuen Cheung, 464-00-95021-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 442, Folder 1)
    - Richardson, James R., IV, 479-00-95037-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 442, Folder 2)
    - Cheung, Betsy, 609-00-20147-203.4 (Box 442, Folder 3)
    - Chow, Wailee, 5055-00-96107-203.000-4, 1996 (Box 442, Folder 4)
    - Chu, Paul Hoi Shan, 100-00-22161-203.3 (Box 442, Folder 5)
    - Hong Kong Institute of Architecture, Wang, Zhu, 464-00-95104-203.000-4 (Box 442, Folder 6)
    - Lam, Andrew, 522-00-99117-203.4, 1999 (Box 442, Folder 7)
    - Li, Man Wei (Tim), 654-00-22138-203.4 (Box 442, Folder 8)
    - Lui, Franklin Tat Man, 654-00-22160-203.4 (Box 443, Folder 1)
    - Mak, Franky Hon Ming, 630-00-21143-203.4 (Box 443, Folder 2)
    - Chan, Brian Yuk Shing, 688-00-24127-203.4 (Box 443, Folder 3)
    - Cheng, Irene Yu Wai, 702-00-24058-203.1 (Box 443, Folder 4)
    - Chinese University of Hong Kong, Nancy Wolf, 693-00-23057-203.1 (Box 443, Folder 5)
  - India, 4.7
    - Kohn, Bernard, B-6740, Inde 1968 (Box 443, Folder 6)
    - Kanvinde, Achyut P., DF-7565, 1975 (Box 444, Folder 1)
    - India International Centre, B-6425, 1964 (Box 444, Folder 2)
    - IIE-Kohn, Bernard, B-6740, 1967 (Box 444, Folder 3)
    - Nerikar, Vasant N., Harvard, B-7201, 1972 (Box 444, Folder 4)
    - Rajan, P.S., IIE, Non-Correspondence, B-6777, 1967 (Box 444, Folder 5)
    - Iie-Rajan, P. S., Architecture-India, Other than Correspondence, B-6777, 1967 (Box 444, Folder 6)
    - Sharma, Mohan N., B-6930, DF-69105, 1969 (Box 444, Folder 7)
    - Zaveri, Anand P., Yale University, EC-7007, EC-7117, 1970-1971 (Box 444, Folder 8)
    - Chermayeff, Serge, B-7047, 1970 (Box 444, Folder 9)
    - Doshi, B. V., DF-6690, DF-6745, 1967 (Box 445, Folder 1)
    - Bose, Supatrik, Harvard University, B-7029, 1970 (Box 445, Folder 2)
    - Asia House Trust, London, Michell and Skelton, B-7743, 1977 (Box 445, Folder 3)
    - Chavda, Alka, B-7709, 1977 (Box 445, Folder 4)
    - Chavda, Vidyadhar, B-7710, 1977 (Box 445, Folder 5)
    - Kulkarni, Praphulla M., B-7612, 1976 (Box 445, Folder 6)
    - Patel, Nimish, B-7614, 1976 (Box 445, Folder 7)
    - Sarabhai, Mana, Yale University, B-7414, 1974 (Box 446, Folder 1)
    - Architecture-Japan, Ushioda, Kazuteru, B-7818, 1978 (Box 446, Folder 2)
    - Asia House Trust, London, Grant Related Materials, B-7743, 1977 (Box 446, Folder 3)
    - Chermayeff, Serge, B-7047, 1970 (Box 446, Folder 4)
    - University of Pennsylvania, DF-8324, 1983 (Box 446, Folder 5)
    - Bhatia, Rajeev, B-8838, 1988 (Box 446, Folder 6)
    - Roy, Avik, B-8839, 1988 (Box 446, Folder 7)
    - Venkataraman, Anuradha, B-9024, 1990 (Box 446, Folder 8)
    - Engel, Peter, B-9364(56), 1993 (Box 447, Folder 1)
    - Judy, Mary Kay, 706-00-22086-203.1 (Box 447, Folder 2)
    - Waronker, Jay, B-90103(56), 1990 (Box 447, Folder 3)